{
  "2": [
    { "prompt": "Εγώ", "answer": "είμαι" },
    { "prompt": "Εσύ", "answer": "είσαι" },
    { "prompt": "Αυτός", "answer": "είναι" },
    { "prompt": "Αυτή", "answer": "είναι" },
    { "prompt": "Αυτό", "answer": "είναι" },
    { "prompt": "είμαι", "answer": "εγώ" },
    { "prompt": "είσαι", "answer": "εσύ" },
    { "prompt": "είναι", "answer": "αυτός/αυτή/αυτό" }
  ],
  "3": [
    { "prompt": "Εγώ", "answer": "έχω" },
    { "prompt": "Εσύ", "answer": "έχεις" },
    { "prompt": "Αυτός", "answer": "έχει" },
    { "prompt": "Αυτή", "answer": "έχει" },
    { "prompt": "Αυτό", "answer": "έχει" },
    { "prompt": "έχω", "answer": "εγώ" },
    { "prompt": "έχεις", "answer": "εσύ" },
    { "prompt": "έχει", "answer": "αυτός/αυτή/αυτό" }
  ]
}
